playwarren.com 2016-04-19

# Play Warren | Privacy Policy

PlayWarren.com (“the Operator”) knows that You care how information about You is used and shared and is committed to protecting your personal information. The Operator wants its services to be safe and enjoyable for everyone. This Policy aims to help you understand what information the Operator might collect about You and how the Operator uses that information.

By visiting the Website having domain name www.PlayWarren.com including any of its sub-domains and links thereon, (and by accessing or using any Service or Software available from the Operator through this Website or which is available for download through third party applications) You are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

The Operator complies with the data protection laws of California. Any personal information provided to or gathered by the Operator is controlled by the Operator (acting as the data controller in terms of data protection laws).

The information gathered about users of the Website helps the Operator personalize and continually improve the experience on the Website and the Services/Software provided to End-Users generally. The Operator uses the information to improve the Website infrastructure and Services/Software offered and to prevent or detect fraud or abuses.

Information is received, stored and processed when you submit information on the Website or through the Services/Software such as providing hand history for data analysis. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of the Website, Services or Software features. The information that you provide is used for purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future services for you and communicating with you.

Certain types of information are processed whenever You interact with the Operator (including for instance through the use of “cookies”, or through email confirmations when You open emails, if your terminal supports such functionality).

The Operator may collect information on which pages of the Operator's Website You visit, IP addresses, the type of browser You use, details of any links which direct you to the Website and the times You access the Operator's Website. This information is used to try to understand customers' preferences better and to manage the load on servers, so as to improve services and your experience generally.

If You send the Operator correspondence, including emails and faxes, information is retained in the records of your account. Customer service correspondence and other correspondence from the Operator to you is also retained in order to keep records of relationships with users, to measure and improve customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of the Operator's terms and conditions. Over time, such records may be deleted if permitted by law.

The Operator may from time to time, offer optional questionnaires and surveys to users for such purposes as collecting demographic information or assessing users' interests and needs. The use of the information collected will be explained in detail in the survey itself. If personally identifiable information is collected from users, users will be given notice of how the information will be used prior to their participation in the survey or questionnaire.

As outlined by this Privacy Policy the Operator shall obtain your contact details for electronic mail in relation to the sale of its products or its Services/Software and therefore may use such details for direct marketing of its own similar products or services. In all correspondence You shall have the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving direct marketing.

Some Software and/or Services provided by the Operator to You may include the possibility of you sending Your hand history to the Operator for the Operator to generate a Player Analysis on your performance. The Operator does not keep copies of such Player Analysis information as this is merely processed and relayed back to you and not stored in any way by the Operator. The user has also the possibility to encrypt the hand history information prior to submitting same to the Operator for analysis. Furthermore, the Operator does not disclose any such processing or data arising therefrom to any other person except the legitimate User.

Visiting the Operator's Websites and/or using the Operator's Services/Software with your browser settings adjusted to accept cookies tells the Operator that you want to use the Operator's products and services and that you consent to the Operator's use of cookies and other technologies to provide them to you as described in this Privacy Policy See below for information on how to modify the settings in your browser to notify you when you receive a new cookie and disable cookies altogether.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's (or other internet-connected device's) hard drive through your Web browser to enable the Operator's systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain ancillary services. Cookies may also be used by the Operator for additional purposes, including:

  1. Identifying You when you sign-in to the Website or Services/Software.
  2. To provide You with product recommendations, to display personalized content, to recognize you as a registered member; amongst other customized features and services the Operator provides.
  3. Keeping track of your specified preferences. This allows the Operator to honor your likes and dislikes, such as whether or not you would like to see certain online advertisements.
  4. Conducting research and diagnostics to improve the Operator's content, products and services;
  5. Preventing fraudulent activities.
  6. Improving security.

The “Help” or “FAQs” on the menu bar of most browsers will explain how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete data used by browser add-ons by amending the add-on's settings.

However please note that cookies allow you to take advantage of some of the Operator's essential features that facilitate your experience. It is therefore recommended that You leave them turned on. If you do leave cookies turned on, be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

Cookies may also be collected by third-party service providers (such as PayPal, Google Analytics, Facebook) offering services through the Website or the Software. If you limit the use of cookies your ability to use such third-party services may be limited. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of the respective service-providers to understand why and how they collect cookies.

Information about You and other users is an important part of the Operator's business and the Operator is not in the business of selling it to others. Information about You and other users is an important part of the Operator's business and the Operator is not in the business of selling it to others.

The Operator shares customer information only as described below and with the Operator's related companies and subsidiaries which the Operator controls and that is either subject to this Privacy Policy or follows practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy.

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

If personal information is transferred to countries outside of the European Economic Area in the course of sharing information as set out above, the Operator will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection.

The Operator works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using encryption software. The Operator maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. The Operator's security procedures may require proof of Your identity before any personal information (including about You) is disclosed to You.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer and it is strongly advisable to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

The Website may include third-party advertising and links to other Websites. The Operator does not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party linked websites who work on their own behalf. The Operator does not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and their information practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

You may access a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with the Website for the purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. As a data subject you may ask the data controller to confirm whether any of your personal data is being processed.

If you have any concern about Your privacy please e-mail the Operator on support@PlayWarren.com with a detailed description of your concerns and the Operator will try to resolve the issue for you.

The Operator's business changes constantly and the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions will change also. The Operator may e-mail periodic reminders of notices and updates, unless you have instructed us not to, but it remains your responsibility to check the Website periodically to see recent changes.
